29 objects imported automatically (use -v 2 for details).

{"domain": "Finance", "summary": "The article argues that capital is rotating from software and 'bits' into 'atoms' or physical industries and materials, driven by AI disruption and the increasing demand for real-world resources. It identifies specific investment opportunities in advanced materials, defense, electrification, aerospace, and nuclear energy, with a detailed focus on Solstice Advanced Materials as a key uranium conversion player.", "difficulty": "Advanced"}
